Now, I don't want to extend these proceedings,
but really to sit there and give answers
like that was a small part of the discussion,
somehow suggesting therefore you didn't have the need
to be full and frank, or it excuses your answers,
doesn't really wash.
I don't think I am making excuses.
I'm explaining.
Those explanations don't hold any water.
Can we move on?
I'm sorry you feel like that.
Yes, I do feel like that.
I'm really sorry you feel like that.
Thank you.
Genuinely, I'm trying to, as per the affirmation I've made,
I'm giving you the truth, the whole truth, and nothing
but the truth.
Right.
And the answers I'm providing to you.
Let's move on to another point.
The Facebook did not inform any of the 270,000 users
or their friends that the information had
been illegitimately accessed, correct?
Well, the 270,000, no, you're correct.
Thank you.
The first time Facebook announced this
was last week, more than two years after it found out
about the breach, correct?
Yes.
Your CEO says in a CNN interview,
I regret we didn't do it at the time.
I think we got that wrong.
You accept that?
Yes, and I've said that already.
And all of this conduct goes against the professed
commitments of Facebook.
I read those out just now, of being transparent about it,